{
    "subject": "resource/Thunderbolt_and_Lightfoot",
    "predicate": "ontology/producer",
    "object": "resource/Robert_Daley_(producer)",
    "human_readable": "Thunderbolt and Lightfoot was produced by Robert Daley.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9204597473144531,
            "question": "Besides Thunderbolt and Lightfoot, what other films might Robert Daley have produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8428012132644653,
            "question": "Who produced the film Thunderbolt and Lightfoot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8248966336250305,
            "question": "What is the profession of Robert Daley in relation to the film Thunderbolt and Lightfoot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8078144788742065,
            "question": "What film was produced by Robert Daley?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7958506345748901,
            "question": "Name a film produced by Robert Daley."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7953926920890808,
            "question": "What is the name of the person who produced Thunderbolt and Lightfoot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6336321830749512,
            "question": "When was the film Thunderbolt and Lightfoot released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5378227233886719,
            "question": "Is Robert Daley known for producing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4010472297668457,
            "question": "What genre is the film Thunderbolt and Lightfoot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2555704414844513,
            "question": "Can you name any actors who starred in Thunderbolt and Lightfoot?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Thunderbolt and Lightfoot was produced by Robert Daley.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3170_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Thunderbolt and Lightfoot?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3170_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Robert Daley known for producing films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3170_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the film Thunderbolt and Lightfoot released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3170_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3170_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3170_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3170_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3170_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3170_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3170_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3170_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3170_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3170_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3170_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in the requested JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis indicates that according to the context information provided, the statement that Thunderbolt and Lightfoot was produced by Robert Daley is supported by the documents. This can be seen from file_path: /Users/stanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3170/re-ranker-msmarco/30.txt which mentions \"written by Michael Cimino ; produced by Robert Daley\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents mentions that \"Thunderbolt and Lightfoot\" was produced by Robert Daley, thus supporting the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}